Finding Aid for James B. Griffin Papers 1922-1997
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- North American Archaeology Card Files, circa 1930s-1990s; 122 linear feet
  - Geographic Areas and Cultures
    - Tennessee
      - Wallace Cave, Site 12 (Box 113)
      - Bullock Cave, Site 13 (Box 113)
      - Hawkins Cave, Site 14 (Box 113)
      - Doan Cave, Site 23 (Box 113)
      - Candy Creek (Box 113)
      - Middle Valley (Box 113)
      - Lenoir Mound 1 (Box 113)
      - Markham (Box 113)
      - Glass-Franklin (Box 113)
      - Mississippi (Box 113)
      - Middle Mississippi (Box 113)
      - Richardsons (Box 113)
      - Hale's Point (Box 113)
      - Shiloh (Box 113)
      - Hiwassee
      - McCarty, Site 4 (Box 113)
      - Irvin, Site 5 (Box 113)
      - Harris Farm, Site 9 (Box 113)
      - Lea Farm, Site 17 (Box 113)
      - Second Culture (Box 113)
      - Rel. (Box 113)
      - De Armond, 2-Re-12 (Box 113)
      - Cherokee -- M.R.H. (Box 113)
      - Dallas (Box 113)
      - Dallas (Box 113)
      - Hixon (Box 113)
      - Bennett Place (Box 113)
      - Hampton Place (Box 113)
      - Citico -- Hamilton Co. (Box 113)
      - Long Island Johnson (Box 113)
      - Johnson Farm, Site 15 (Box 113)
      - Walters, Site 11 (Box 113)
      - Ausmus, Site 10 (Box 113)
      - Cox Mound, Site 19 (Box 113)
      - 1. Je (Box 114)
      - Yarnell Component (Box 114)
      - Hiwassee Island, Mg31 (Box 114)
      - Lenoir Island Mound 2 (Box 114)
      - Lick Creek (Box 114)
      - McMurray Mound 2 (Box 114)
      - McSpaddin-Citico (Box 114)
      - Calloway-Toca (Box 114)
      - McGee (Box 114)
      - Stratton (Box 114)
      - Mouse Creeks (Box 114)
      - Rymer Place, 15By11 (Box 114)
    - Georgia
      - General (Box 115)
      - Georgia Pottery Types (Box 115)
      - Stallings Island (Box 115)
      - Bilbo (Box 115)
      - Deptford (Box 115)
      - Wilmington (Box 115)
      - Swift Creek (Box 115)
      - Ossabaw Island, Mound C (Box 115)
      - Ossabaw Island, Mound D (Box 115)
      - Weeden Island (Box 115)
      - Hare's Landing (Box 115)
      - Swift Creek (Box 115)
      - Savannah (Box 115)
      - Lake Bluff (Box 115)
      - Shell Bluff (Box 115)
      - South-End Settlement (Box 115)
      - Lawton's Field (Box 115)
      - Townsend Mound (Box 115)
      - Rockmart (Box 115)
      - Lamar (Box 115)
      - Suwanee (Box 115)
      - Bull Creek (Box 115)
      - Kyle (Box 115)
      - Turnbull (Box 115)
      - Nacoochee (Box 115)
      - Cartersville (Box 115)
      - Hollywood (Box 115)
      - Kolomoki (Box 115)
      - Neisler (Box 115)
      - Carroll (Box 115)
      - Lamar (Box 115)
      - Irene (Box 115)
      - Walker Mound (Box 115)
      - Creighton Island (Box 115)
      - Darien (Box 115)
      - Dumoussay's Field (Box 115)
      - Bourbon (Box 115)
      - Ossabaw Island, Mound A (Box 115)
      - Ossabaw Island, Mound B (Box 115)
      - Bluff Field (Box 115)
      - Hudson's Ferry (Box 115)
      - Mitchell's Lake (Box 115)
      - Macon Plateau (Box 115)
      - Macon Mound A (Box 115)
      - Macon Mound C (Box 115)
      - Middle Plateau (Box 115)
      - Trading Post (Box 115)
      - Holton Shoals (Box 115)
      - Mossy Oak (Box 115)
      - Wilkerson Lake (Box 115)
      - Etowah
        - Etowah Mound C (Box 116)
        - Etowah General (Box 116)
        - Etowah La Mar Village Site
          - 1962 (Box 116)
          - 1964 (Box 116)
          - 1965 (Box 117)
        - Dougherty Co. (Box 117)
        - Miscellaneous -- Georgia (Box 117)
    - South Carolina
      - General (Box 117)
      - Oemler Site (Box 117)
      - Little Island (Box 117)
      - Chester Field (Box 117)
      - Thom's Creek (Box 117)
      - Lake Plantation (Box 117)
      - Cutoff Island (Box 117)
      - Evelyn Mound (Box 117)
    - Caribbean (Box 117)
    - Southwest (Box 117)
    - Alabama
      - Ft. Toulouse (Box 118)
      - Fusihatchie (Box 118)
      - Tukabahcie (Box 118)
      - Hoithlewali (Box 118)
      - Hope Hull (Box 118)
      - Pintlala Creek (Box 118)
      - Pt. Comfort (Box 118)
      - Mitylene (Box 118)
      - Connolly Place (Box 118)
      - Atasi (Box 118)
      - Old Augusta (Box 118)
      - Ecumhutka (Box 118)
      - Ashley Place (Box 118)
      - Catoma Creek Village Site (Box 118)
      - Provenance Unknown -- Specimens from Collections in Montgomery, AL (Box 118)
      - University of Chicago Alabama Pictorial Survey Duplicates (Box 118)
    - Florida
      - Florida -- General (Box 118)
      - Florida Pottery Types (Box 118)
      - Alligator Bayou (Box 118)
      - St. John's (Box 118)
      - St. John's Shell Mounds (Box 118)
      - St. John's Bluff (Box 118)
      - Rice Creek (Box 118)
      - Palatka (Box 118)
      - Murphys Island (Box 118)
      - Buffalo Bluff (Box 118)
      - Horse Landing (Box 118)
      - Rocky Point (Box 118)
      - Drayton-Rembrandt (Box 118)
      - Salt Run (Box 118)
      - Silver Spring (Box 118)
      - Ropes Island (Box 118)
      - Volusia Bar (Box 118)
      - Hitchen's Creek (Box 118)
      - Morrison's Creek (Box 118)
      - Fort Butler (Box 118)
      - Mt. Taylor (Box 118)
      - Bird's Island (Box 118)
      - Bluffton (Box 118)
      - Bartram's (Box 118)
      - Lake Dexter (Box 118)
      - DeLeon Springs (Box 118)
      - Tick Island (Box 118)
      - St. Francis (Box 118)
      - Old Town (Box 118)
      - Hawkinsville (Box 118)
      - Lake Beresford (Box 118)
      - Alexander's Springs (Box 118)
      - Alicia (Box 118)
      - Huntoon Island (Box 118)
      - Blue Spring -- Shell (Box 118)
      - Wekiva (Box 118)
      - Enterprise (Box 118)
      - Spear's Landing (Box 118)
      - Black Hammock (Box 118)
      - Daniel's (Box 118)
      - Watson's Landing (Box 118)
      - Cook's Ferry (Box 118)
      - Solee's Landing (Box 118)
      - Econlockhatchee (Box 118)
      - Orange Mound (Box 118)
      - Long Bluff (Box 118)
      - Mulberry Mound (Box 118)
      - Rattlesnake Hammock (Box 118)
      - South Indian Field (Box 118)
      - St. George Island (Box 118)
      - East Coast (Box 118)
      - Lighthouse (Box 118)
      - Gleason (Box 118)
      - Ocklawaha (Box 118)
      - Hopson Mound (Box 118)
      - Old Okahumpka (Box 118)
      - Helena (Box 118)
      - Silver Springs (Box 118)
      - Higley Lake (Box 118)
      - Umatilla Mound (Box 118)
      - Gamble Mound (Box 119)
      - Tavares (Box 119)
      - Ormond (Box 119)
      - St. Johns Sand Mounds (Box 119)
      - Summer Haven (Box 119)
      - Johnson Mound (Box 119)
      - Mill Cove (Box 119)
      - Gilbert Mound (Box 119)
      - Shields Mound (Box 119)
      - Grant Mound (Box 119)
      - Low Mounds -- Grant (Box 119)
      - Monroe Mound (Box 119)
      - Horseshoe Landing (Box 119)
      - Broward Mound (Box 119)
      - Reddie Point (Box 119)
      - Denton Mound (Box 119)
      - Chaseville (Box 119)
      - Floral Bluff (Box 119)
      - Daniel's Landing (Box 119)
      - Arlington (Box 119)
      - South Jacksonville (Box 119)
      - Point La Vista (Box 119)
      - Mulberry Grove (Box 119)
      - Beauclerc (Box 119)
      - Julington Creek (Box 119)
      - Mandarin Point (Box 119)
      - Peoria (Box 119)
      - Bayard Point (Box 119)
      - Harris Mound (Box 119)
      - Picolata (Box 119)
      - Racey Point (Box 119)
      - Fruit Cove (Box 119)
      - Deep Creek (Box 119)
      - East Palatka (Box 119)
      - St. John's Landing (Box 119)
      - Murphy Island (Box 119)
      - Dunn's Creek (Box 119)
      - Davenport (Box 119)
      - Tick Island -- Sand (Box 119)
      - Thursby Mound (Box 119)
      - Huntoon Island (Box 119)
      - Stark's Grove, Lake Beresford (Box 119)
      - Blue Spring -- Sand (Box 119)
      - Fort Florida (Box 119)
      - Ginn's Grove (Box 119)
      - Lake Monroe, Northern End (Box 119)
      - Thornhill Lake (Box 119)
      - Cook's Ferry (Box 119)
      - Mansfield's (Box 119)
      - Raulerson's (Box 119)
      - Persimmon Mound (Box 119)
      - Indian Fields (Box 119)
      - Mulberry (Box 119)
      - Fort Taylor (Box 119)
      - Mt. Royal (Box 120)
      - Punta Rassa (Box 120)
      - Mt. Royal (Box 120)
      - Norwalk Landing (Box 120)
      - Hitchen's Creek (Box 120)
      - Blue Creek (Box 120)
      - Near Duval's (Box 120)
      - Bluffton (Box 120)
      - Pine Woods (Box 120)
      - Volusia (Box 120)
      - Ft. Walton (Box 120)
      - Santa Rosa (Box 120)
      - Near Jolly Bay (Box 120)
      - Walton's Camp (Box 120)
      - Cemetery Near Point Washington (Box 120)
      - Mound Near Point Washington (Box 120)
      - Crystal River (Box 120)
      - Anderson's Bayou (Box 120)
      - Cemetery Near Carrabelle (Box 120)
      - Weeden Island (Box 120)
      - Safford (Box 120)
      - Near Rocky Bayou (Box 120)
      - Near River Basin (Box 120)
      - Point Washington (Box 120)
      - Near Douglas Bluff (Box 120)
      - Spring Hill Landing (Box 120)
      - Miller Field Landing (Box 120)
      - McLaney Place (Box 120)
      - Near Pippen's Lake (Box 120)
      - Hogtown Bayou (Box 120)
      - Near West Bay Creek (Box 120)
      - West of Burnt Mill Creek (Box 120)
      - Near Davis Point (Box 120)
      - Wise Bluff (Box 120)
      - Near Crooked Island (Box 120)
      - Near Rock Bluff (Box 120)
      - Near Hardnut Landing (Box 120)
      - Bird Hammock (Box 120)
      - Lewis Place (Box 120)
      - Cemetery Cedar Keys (Box 120)
      - Bear Point (Box 120)
      - West Coast (Box 120)
      - Chokoloskee (Box 120)
      - Near Maester Creek (Box 120)
      - Near Farmdale (Box 120)
      - Wiggins Key (Box 120)
      - Pine Island (Box 120)
      - Peter's Creek (Box 120)
      - Hickory Bluff (Box 120)
      - Gasparilla Sound (Box 120)
      - Ten Thousand Islands (Box 120)
      - Goodland Point (Box 120)
    - Central Mississippi Valley Archaeological Survey
      - General (Box 121)
      - Site Cards
        - 9-0, Lawhorn (Box 121)
        - 10-P-1, Carson Lake (Box 121)
        - 10-P-2, Bell Place (Box 121)
        - 10-P-3, Nettle Ridge (Box 121)
        - 10-P-4, Notgrass Place (Box 121)
        - 10-Q1, Upper Nodena (Box 121)
        - 10-Q-2, Sherman Mound (Box 121)
        - 10-Q-3, Turnage Mound (Box 121)
        - 11-N-1, Parkin Mound (Box 121)
        - 11-N-2, Rogers Place (Box 121)
        - 11-N-3, Roberts Site (Box 121)
        - 11-N-4, Neeley's Ferry (Box 121)
        - 11-N-5, White Place (Box 121)
        - 11-N-6, Block Site (Box 121)
        - 11-N-7, Harold Site (Box 121)
        - 11-N-8, Williams Site (Box 121)
        - 11-N-9, Vernon Paul (Box 121)
        - 11-N-10, Cross County Club (Box 121)
        - 11-N-11, Delta Site (Box 121)
        - 11-N-12, Turbow Place (Box 121)
        - 11-N-13, Williamson Site (Box 121)
        - 11-N-14, Twist No. 1 (Box 121)
        - 11-N-15, Fortune Mound (Box 121)
        - 11-N-16, Twist Group (Box 121)
        - 11-N-17, Cherry Valley (Box 122)
        - 11-O-1, Pittman Site (Box 122)
        - 11-O-2, Webster Cemetery (Box 122)
        - 11-O-3, Emrich Place (Box 122)
        - 11-O-4, Cummins Place (Box 122)
        - 11-O-5, Emory Site (Box 122)
        - 11-O-6, Pinkston Site (Box 122)
        - 11-O-7, Lewis Place (Box 122)
        - 11-O-8, Richard Bridge (Box 122)
        - 11-O-9, Gilliland Site (Box 122)
        - 11-O-10, Barton Ranch (Box 122)
        - 11-O-11, Prosperity Place (Box 122)
        - 11-O-12, Black Oak Church (Box 122)
        - 11-P-1, Shawnee Village (Box 122)
        - 11-P-2, Bradley (Banks and Danner)
          - Banks (Perino) (Box 123)
          - Wapanoca (Box 123)
        - 11-P-3, Golightly Place (Box 123)
        - 11-P-4, Pacific Site (Box 123)
        - 11-P-5, Lambethville (Box 123)
        - 12-N-2, Manly Site (Box 123)
        - 12-N-3, Rose Mound (Box 123)
        - 12-N-4, Big Eddy (Box 123)
        - 12-N-5, Welshans Place (Box 123)
        - 12-N-6, Westmorland Site (Box 123)
        - 12-N-7, Lansing Site (Box 123)
        - 12-N-8, Beckles Site (Box 123)
        - 12-N-9, Burns Site (Box 123)
        - 12-N-10, DeRossett's Place (Box 123)
        - 12-N-11, Johnson Site (Box 123)
        - 12-N-12, Widener Cemetery (Box 123)
        - 12-N-13, Parks Site (Box 123)
        - 12-N-14, Crow Creek (Box 123)
        - 12-N-15, Swan Place (Box 123)
        - 12-O-1, Turner Place (Box 123)
        - 12-O-2, Pouncey Site (Box 123)
        - 12-O-3, Thompson Lake (Box 123)
        - 12-O-4, Davis Place (Box 123)
        - 12-O-5, Cramor Place (Box 123)
        - 12-O-6, Brackenseed Place (Box 123)
        - 12-P-1, Mound Place (Box 123)
        - 12-P-2, Shelby (U. Tenn. Site) (Box 123)
        - 13-M-1, Hughes Site (Box 123)
        - 13-N-1, Suden Cemetery (Box 123)
        - 13-N-2, Alligator Bayou (Box 123)
        - 13-N-3, Mound Cemetery Site (Box 123)
        - 13-N-4, Kent Place (Box 123)
        - 13-N-5, Davis Site (Box 124)
        - 13-N-6, Jerusalem Church (Box 124)
        - 13-N-7, Clay Hill (Box 124)
        - 13-N-8, Findley (Box 124)
        - 13-N-9, Red Oak Site (Box 124)
        - 13-N-10, Taylor Mound (Box 124)
        - 13-N-11, Grant Place (Box 124)
        - 13-N-12, Murdock Place (Box 124)
        - 13-N-13, Rawlison Site (Box 124)
        - 13-N-14, Conner Place (Box 124)
        - 13-N-15, Nickel Site (Box 124)
        - 13-N-16, Starkley Site (Box 124)
        - 13-N-17, Greer Site (Box 124)
        - 13-N-18, Lakeside (Box 124)
        - 13-N-19, Riverside Site (Box 124)
        - 13-N-20, Hargrave Site (Box 124)
        - 13-N-21, Castile Landing (Box 124)
        - 13-O-1, Barrett Site (Box 124)
        - 13-O-2, Green River (Box 124)
        - 13-O-3, Huber Site (Box 124)
        - 13-O-4, Nickey Mound (Box 124)
        - 13-O-5, Belle Meade (Box 124)
        - 13-O-6, New Bethel (Box 124)
        - 13-O-7, Beck Site (Box 124)
        - 13-O-8, Stoddard Site (Box 124)
        - 13-O-9, Collins Site (Box 124)
        - 13-O-10, Hollywood (Box 124)
        - 13-O-11, Commerce (Box 124)
        - 13-O-13, Crystal Springs Mound (Box 124)
        - 13-O-14, Sledge (Box 124)
        - 13-P-1, Walls (Box 124)
        - 13-P-2, Edgefield Mounds (Box 124)
        - 13-P-3, Turkey Ridge (Box 124)
        - 13-P-4, Dogwood Ridge (Box 124)
        - 13-P-5, Shannon (Box 124)
        - 13-P-6, Cheatham (Box 124)
        - 13-P-7, Norfolk (Box 124)
        - 13-P-8, Lake Cormorant (Box 124)
        - 13-P-9, Withers (Box 124)
        - 13-P-10, Irby (Box 124)
        - 13-P-11, Woodlyn (Box 124)
        - 14-L-1, Webster's Camp (Box 124)
        - 14-M-1, Turner Site (Box 124)
        - 14-M-2, Bonner Site (Box 124)
        - 14-M-3, Broom Site (Box 124)
        - 14-N-1, Moore Site (Box 124)
        - 14-N-2, Steagall Site (Box 124)
        - 14-N-3, McCullough (Box 124)
        - 14-N-4, Bowie Village Site (Box 124)
        - 14-N-5, Coolidge Mound (Box 124)
        - 14-N-6, Helena Crossing (Box 124)
        - 14-O-1, Evansville (Box 124)
        - 14-O-2, Owens Site (Box 124)
        - 14-O-3, Beaverdam Site (Box 124)
        - 14-O-4, Mhoon Landing (Box 124)
        - 14-O-5, McKinney Bayou (Box 124)
        - 14-O-6, Johnson Mound (Box 124)
        - 14-O-7, Oakwood Cemetery (Box 124)
        - 14-O-8, Dundee (Box 124)
        - 14-O-9, Norflett (Box 125)
        - 14-O-10, West Mounds (Box 125)
        - 14-O-11, Kendall Mound (Box 125)
        - 14-O-12, Jepson (Box 125)
        - 14-O-13, Canon (Box 125)
        - 14-P-1, McKane (Box 125)
        - 14-P-2, Prichard (Box 125)
        - 15-L-1, Butler Mound (Box 125)
        - 15-L-2, Baytown Site (Box 125)
        - 15-L-3, Hall Site (Box 125)
        - 15-M-1, Tinsley Mound (Box 125)
        - 15-M-2, Elaine Site (Box 125)
        - 15-M-3, Elaine Consolidated School Mound (Box 125)
        - 15-M-4, Crow Site (Box 125)
        - 15-M-5, Vogel Mounds (Box 125)
        - 15-N-1, Fitzhugh (Box 125)
        - 15-N-2, Ellis Site (Box 125)
        - 15-N-3, Old Town (Box 125)
        - 15-N-4, Buie Site (Box 125)
        - 15-N-6, Montgomery Site (Box 125)
        - 15-N-7, Stovall Mound (Box 125)
        - 15-N-8, Carson Group (Box 125)
        - 15-N-9, Vaught Mound (Box 125)
        - 15-N-10, Dickerson (Box 125)
        - 15-O-1, Salomon-Hull (Box 125)
        - 15-O-2, Barbee (Box 125)
        - 15-O-3, Maddox (Box 125)
        - 15-O-4, Lula (Box 125)
        - 15-O-5, Moon (Box 125)
        - 15-O-6, Posey (Box 125)
        - 15-O-7, Prowell (Box 125)
        - 15-O-8, Gates (Box 125)
        - 15-O-9, Hull Brake (Box 125)
        - 15-O-10, Wilford (Box 125)
        - 15-O-11, Morrison (Box 125)
        - 15-O-12, D'Orr (Box 125)
        - 15-O-13, Allison (Box 125)
        - 15-O-14, Youngblood (Box 125)
        - 15-O-15, Whiting (Box 125)
        - 15-O-16, Tidwell (Box 125)
        - 15-O-17, Miller Place (Box 125)
        - 15-O-18, Ware (Box 125)
        - 15-P-1, Thomas (Box 125)
        - 15-P-2, Taylor (Box 125)
        - 15-P-3, Indian Creek (Box 125)
        - 15-P-4, Corn Lake (Box 125)
        - McCarter (Box 125)
        - 16-K-1, Jones Place (Old River Ldg) (Box 125)
        - 16-K-2, Mill Bayou Prairie (Box 125)
        - 16-K-3, McGahhey Site (Box 125)
        - 16-L-1, Bitely Place (Box 125)
        - 16-L-2, Essex Site (Box 125)
        - 16-L-3, Stovall (Box 125)
        - 16-L-4, Brandenburg A (Box 125)
        - 16-L-5, Brandenburg B (Box 125)
        - 16-L-6, Dupree Site (Box 125)
        - 16-M-1, Avenue (Box 125)
        - 16-M-2, Tomanelli (Box 125)
        - 16-M-3, Yates (Box 125)
        - 16-M-4, Macedonia (Box 125)
        - 16-M-5, Mt. Olive (Box 125)
        - 16-M-6, Stokes Bayou (Box 125)
        - 16-M-7, Brook Bayou (Box 125)
        - 16-N-1, Acree Place (Box 125)
        - 16-N-2, Alligator Mounds (Box 125)
        - 16-N-3, Ellis (Box 125)
        - 16-N-4, Rufus Davis (Box 125)
        - 16-N-5 (Box 125)
        - 16-N-6, Oliver (Box 125)
        - 16-N-7, Bramlett (Box 125)
        - 16-N-8, Peter's Rock (Box 125)
        - 16-N-9, Mattson (Box 125)
        - 16-N-10, Myer (Box 125)
        - 16-N-11, Hopson Bayou (Box 125)
        - 16-N-12, Black Bayou (Box 125)
        - 16-N-13, Sherard (Box 125)
        - 16-N-14, Harris Bayou (Box 125)
        - 16-N-15, Dogwood Bayou (Box 125)
        - 16-N-16, Baugh (Box 125)
        - 16-N-17, Howden Lake (Box 125)
        - 16-N-18, Bobo (Box 125)
        - 16-N-19, Crawford Lake (Box 125)
        - 16-N-20, Aderholt (Box 125)
        - 16-N-21, Morning Star (Box 125)
        - 16-N-22, Clark (Box 125)
        - 16-N-23, Hopson (Box 125)
        - 16-N-24, Durham (Box 125)
        - 16-N-25, Doadey (Box 125)
        - 16-O-1, Dunn (Box 125)
        - 16-O-2, Spendthrift (Box 125)
        - 16-O-3, Everett (Box 125)
        - 16-O-4, Opposum Bayou (Box 125)
        - 16-O-5, Yager (Box 125)
        - 16-O-6, Garmon (Box 125)
        - 16-O-7, Henderson (Box 125)
        - 16-O-8, Norman (Box 125)
        - 16-O-9, Little Texas (Box 125)
        - 16-O-10, Vance (Box 125)
        - 16-O-11, Oxbow Bend (Box 125)
        - 16-O-12, Oliverfried (Box 125)
        - 16-O-13, Denton (Box 125)
        - 16-O-14, Stover (Box 125)
        - 16-O-15, Garner (Box 125)
        - 16-O-16, Flower (Box 125)
        - 16-O-17, Longstreet (Box 125)
        - 16-P-1, Charleston (Box 125)
        - 16-P-2, Shady Grove (Box 125)
        - 16-P-3, Twin Lakes (Box 125)
        - 16-P-4, White (Box 125)
        - 16-P-5, Crosslyn (Box 125)
        - 16-P-6, Cox (Box 125)
        - 16-P-7, Mitchell (Box 125)
        - 16-P-8, Blue Lake (Box 125)
        - 16-P-9, Carmichael (Box 125)
        - 16-P-10, Long Lake (Box 125)
        - 17-K-1, Menard Mound (Box 125)
        - 17-K-2, Thiele Hill (Box 125)
        - 17-K-3, Wallace (Box 125)
        - 17-K-4, Almond Farm (Box 125)
        - 17-K-5, Cooks Mound (Box 125)
        - 17-K-6, Bond Site (Box 125)
        - 17-K-7, Alma Brown (Box 125)
        - 17-L-1, Massey Place (Box 125)
        - 17-L-2, Ellerton Mound (Box 125)
        - 17-L-3, Poor Place (Box 125)
        - 17-L-4, Wynn Site (Box 125)
        - 17-L-5, Waxhaw (Box 125)
        - 17-M-1, Bear Ridge (Box 125)
        - 17-M-2, Blanchard (Box 125)
        - 17-M-3, Perthshire (Box 125)
        - 17-M-4, Christmas (Box 125)
        - 17-M-5, Walton (Box 125)
        - 17-M-6, Mound City (Box 125)
        - 17-M-7, Moore (Box 125)
        - 17-M-8, Bob Williams (Box 125)
        - 17-M-9, Spinks (Box 125)
        - 17-M-10, Reynolds (Box 125)
        - 17-M-11, Bush (Box 125)
        - 17-M-12, O'Donnell (Box 125)
        - 17-M-13, Boles Lake (Box 125)
        - 17-M-14, Boykin Bogue (Box 126)
        - 17-M-15, Dattel (Box 126)
        - 17-M-16, MacGowan (Box 126)
        - 17-M-17, Nelson (Box 126)
        - 17-M-18, Roosevelt (Box 126)
        - 17-M-19, Firtell (Box 126)
        - 17-M-20, Shelby (Box 126)
        - 17-M-21, Laban Bayou (Box 126)
        - 17-N-1, Merigold (Box 126)
        - 17-N-2, Walford (Box 126)
        - 17-N-3, Debow (Box 126)
        - 17-N-4, Penitentiary (Box 126)
        - 17-N-5, May (Box 126)
        - 17-N-6, Dodd (Box 126)
        - 17-N-7, Baltzer (Box 126)
        - 17-N-8, Boyer (Box 126)
        - 17-N-9, L.L. Vance (Box 126)
        - 17-N-10, Nora Smith (Box 126)
        - 17-N-11, Dockery (Box 126)
        - 17-N-12, Long Lake (Box 126)
        - 17-N-13, Burnet (Box 126)
        - 17-N-14, Kimball (Box 126)
        - 17-N-15, Cook (Box 126)
        - 17-N-16, Wilnot (Box 126)
        - 17-N-17, John Dickson (Box 126)
        - 17-N-18, Joe Smith (Box 126)
        - 17-N-19, Parker (Box 126)
        - 17-N-20, Newton Bayou (Box 126)
        - 17-N-21, Loosangle (Box 126)
        - 17-O-1, Buford (Box 126)
        - 17-O-2, James (Box 126)
        - 17-O-3, Petty (Box 126)
        - 17-O-4, Flaut (Box 126)
        - 17-O-5, King Mound Group (Box 126)
        - 17-O-6, Jernberg (Box 126)
        - 17-O-7, Jacobs (Box 126)
        - 17-O-8, Falls (Box 126)
        - 17-O-9, Powell Bayou (Box 126)
        - 17-O-10, Sage (Box 126)
        - 17-O-11, Cassiby Bayou (Box 126)
        - 17-O-12, Rome (Box 126)
        - 17-P-1, Tippo Bayou (Box 126)
        - 17-P-2, Cason (Box 126)
        - 18-K-1, Hogg Lake (Box 126)
        - 18-K-2, Westlake Site (Box 126)
        - 18-L-1, Neblett Landing (Box 126)
        - 18-M-1, Ferracci-Feretti (Box 126)
        - 18-M-2, Noble (Box 126)
        - 18-M-3, Stringtown (Box 126)
        - 18-M-4, Lipe (Box 126)
        - 18-M-5, Brooks (Box 126)
        - 19-L-1, Blum Site (Box 126)
        - 19-L-2, Bachelor Bend (Box 126)
        - 19-L-3, Ely (Box 126)
        - 19-L-4, Deer Creek (Box 126)
        - 19-L-5, Ireland (Box 126)
        - 19-L-6, Refuge (Box 126)
        - 19-L-7, Ash Bayou (Box 126)
        - 19-M-1, Leland (Avondale) (Box 126)
        - 19-M-2, Sheldon (Box 126)
        - 19-M-3, Stoneville (Box 126)
        - 19-M-4, Dunleith (Box 126)
        - 19-M-5, Holly Knowe (Box 126)
        - 19-M-6, Arcola High School (Box 126)
        - 19-N-1, Kinlock (Box 126)
        - 19-N-2, Shields (Box 126)
        - 19-N-3, Bay Lake (Box 126)
        - 19-N-4, Danzler (Box 126)
        - 19-N-5, Failing (Box 126)
        - 20-L-2, Silver Lake (Box 126)
        - 20-M-1, Arcola (Box 126)
        - 20-M-2, Deer Creek (Box 126)
        - 20-M-3, Panther Burn (Box 126)
        - 20-M-4, Bear Garden (Box 126)
        - 20-M-5, Swan Lake (Box 126)
        - 20-M-6, Clower (Box 126)
        - 20-N-1, Midnight (Box 126)
        - 20-N-2, Summerfield (Box 126)
        - 20-N-3, Straight Bayou (Box 126)
        - 20-O-1, Jaketown (Box 126)
        - 20-O-2, Belzoni (Box 126)
        - 20-O-3, Lamkin (Box 126)
        - 20-O-4, Atchafalaya Bayou (Box 126)
        - 20-O-5, Silver City (Box 126)
        - 20-O-6, Golson (Box 126)
        - 21-M-1, Rolling Fork (Box 126)
        - 21-N-1, Lake George (Box 126)